<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.elenintech.capicopy</id>
    <name>Capi Copy</name>
    <version>1.1.0</version>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <vendor email="eleninjaytech@gmail.com" url="https://eleninjaytech.github.io/public">ELENIN Tech</vendor>

    <description>
        <![CDATA[
        <h3>Tired of manually formatting code for AI assistants like ChatGPT or Gemini?</h3>
        <p><strong>Capi Copy is the essential copy-and-paste tool for developers.</strong> It formats your code, including file paths and line numbers, perfectly for any AI prompt with a single shortcut. Stop wasting time and boost your productivity!</p>

        <p style="text-align:center;">
            </p>

        <h3>Key Features & Benefits</h3>
        <ul>
            <li>
                <strong>✨ AI-Optimized Prompts:</strong> Instantly formats file paths, line numbers, and code into a structure that Large Language Models (LLM) like GPT and Gemini understand best. Get better, more accurate answers from your AI assistant.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>⚡️ Precise Context at Your Fingertips:</strong> Need to ask about a specific part of your code? Simply select the text to copy it with exact line numbers, giving your AI the precise context it needs for debugging or refactoring.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>🚀 Boost Your Workflow:</strong> Double-press the shortcut to copy all open files at once. Drastically reduce the time spent on manual copy-pasting and stay focused on what truly matters: coding. This is a must-have for prompt engineering.
            </li>
            <li>
                <strong>🎨 Seamless Integration:</strong> Comes with beautiful icons that adapt to both light and dark IDE themes for a native look and feel.
            </li>
        </ul>

        <hr/>
        <p><strong>💛 If you enjoy this productivity tool, please support me with a <a href="https://www.buymeacoffee.com/eleninjaytech">cup of coffee</a>!</strong></p>
        <hr/>
        <p><i>Keywords: GPT, Gemini, AI Assistant, ChatGPT, LLM, Prompt, Prompt Engineering, Generative AI, Copy Paste, Developer Tools, Productivity, Code Tools, Editor</i></p>
        ]]>
    </description>

    <change-notes>
        <![CDATA[
        Initial release with path/content copy options and double-click multi-file support.
        ]]>
    </change-notes>

    <actions>
        <action id="org.example.CopyFilePathAndContentAction"
                class="org.example.actions.CopyFilePathAndContentAction"
                text="Copy File Path &amp; Content"
                description="Copies the current file path and content to clipboard">
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu" anchor="last"/>
            <keyboard-shortcut keymap="$default" first-keystroke="ctrl shift alt Q" />
        </action>
    </actions>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <notificationGroup id="Custom Notification Group" displayType="BALLOON" />

        <applicationConfigurable
                id="org.example.copyfilepathandcontent.settings"
                displayName="Capi Copy Settings"
                implementation="org.example.settings.CopyPluginConfigurable"
                groupId="tools" />
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>